// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the chapter president?",
    answer: "Julius John Kehinde",
    options: [
      "Kehinde Julius John",
      "John Julius Kehinde",
      "Julius Kehinde John",
      "Julius John Kehinde"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the title of the sermon preached by Bro Olarewaju Daniel on Feb 5, 2023?",
    answer: "Comfort in the storm",
    options: [
      "Comforted in the storm",
      "Comforted by the storm",
      "Comfort in the storm",
      "Comfort during the storm"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "'He considered the reproach of Christ greater wealth than the treasures of Egypt, for he was looking to the reward.'.. Who is the Bible talking about?",
    answer: "Moses",
    options: [
      "Joseph",
      "Jacob",
      "Paul",
      "Moses"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "For I know the thoughts that I think toward you, saith the Lord , thoughts of peace, and not of evil, to give you an expected end",
    answer: "Jeremiah 29:11",
    options: [
      "Jeremiah 29:12",
      "Jeremiah 29:19",
      "Jeremiah 29:11",
      "Jeremiah 29:13"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "And ye shall know the truth, and the truth shall ____ you free. John 8:32 KJV",
    answer: "make",
    options: [
      "set",
      "make",
      "maketh",
      "call"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How old was Manasseh when he began to reign?",
    answer: "twelve",
    options: [
      "twelve",
      "eight",
      "twenty",
      "twenty-one"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The lines are fallen unto me in pleasant places ; yea, I have a goodly heritage.",
    answer: "Psalm 16:6",
    options: [
      "Psalm 45:7",
      "Psalm 16:6",
      "Psalm 18:18",
      "Psalm 6:16"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "For it is not possible that the blood of ___ and of ___ should take away sins. Hebrews 10:4 KJV",
    answer: "bulls, goats",
    options: [
      "pigeons, goats",
      "sheep, birds",
      "fowls, rams",
      "bulls, goats"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Thus saith the Lord; Cursed be the man that trusteth in man,...",
    answer: "Jeremiah 17:5",
    options: [
      "Jeremiah 17:5",
      "Jeremiah 5:2",
      "Jeremiah 15:5",
      "Jeremiah 1:7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Yet ___ the archangel, when contending with the devil he disputed about the body of Moses,...Jude 1:9 KJV",
    answer: "Michael",
    options: [
      "Michael",
      "Gabriel",
      "Emmanuel",
      "Afoda Noah"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];